<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on Monika&#39;s Statistics</title>
    <link>/categories/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on Monika&#39;s Statistics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Portfolio VaR</title>
      <link>/2018/03/19/crypto-portfolio-var/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/19/crypto-portfolio-var/</guid>
      <description>Analysis based on data available at 2018-03-20 01:00:00Note: data is random, anytrading strategies that
Marginal Log-ReturnsHere is descriptive analysis of historical returns. See mean, median, min and max value for each cryptocurrency from 2017-09-01 02:00:00 to 2018-03-20 01:00:00:
The historical means of the data are the following:
## BCH BTC ETH LTC ## 0.003 0.003 0.002 0.003The historical variance of data is the following:
## BCH BTC ETH LTC ## 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trial</title>
      <link>/2018/02/23/trial/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/23/trial/</guid>
      <description>R MarkdownThis is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
When you click the Knit button a document will be generated that includes both content as well as the output of any embedded R code chunks within the document. You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars)## speed dist ## Min.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rotavirus childhood vaccination in Sweden</title>
      <link>/2015/07/23/rotavirus-childhood-vaccination-in-sweden/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/07/23/rotavirus-childhood-vaccination-in-sweden/</guid>
      <description>Rotavirus is a childhood disease and the leading cause of severe diarrhea in children aged less than five years. This infection is associated with significant mortality in developing countries and high financial burdens worldwide. The incubation time of rotavirus is around 2 days while severe symptoms last for approximately 4-8 days (“Rotavirus | About Rotavirus | CDC” 2015). The median age at the primary rotavirus infection ranges from six to nine months in low income countries, while in high income countries the first episode may occasionally be delayed until the age of two to five years; the majority of incidences however, still occurs in infancy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>